greatvectors.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy :: Vexels

Thanks for using Vexels. When users dip into [www.vexels.com](http://www.vexels.com/), some basic information is collected. In this Privacy Policy you can learn more about the data we collect, what we do with it and how our handling procedures work. This Policy only applies to our website and you can always contact us if you have any questions. We take your privacy very seriously and we will never share or sell your information.  

Vexels is operated by Dugson Digital SRL, with business office at Almirante Harwood 6169, Montevideo Uruguay postal code 11500 (hereinafter, referred to as 'Vexels',“we”, “our, “us”), which acts as the Data Controller. Vexels collects from the individual user (hereinafter, referred to as “you” or “your”) certain information through the website [http://www.vexels.com](http://www.vexels.com/) (hereinafter, referred to as “the Website”, 'the Site', 'Our Site'). This Privacy Policy applies only and exclusively to this Website.

### What type of Personal Information we collect 

1\. We collect some personal information about visitors and users of our site.

2\. The information we might collect is: email address, name, username, IP address, avatar photo, website, occupation, activity, address, location and interests. If you make purchases we might collect tax information, transaction ID, company name and address. We might collect other type of information like preferences and feedback from your support queries, emails and live chats.

### When we collect personal information

**  
** 1\. When you message us using our contact form we collect : (1) your name and (2) your email address This information is used for the purpose of replying to your inquiries. 

2\. When you create an account on the Website, we collect the following Personal Information from you: (1) your name/username; (2) your email address, (3) the country/location where you are signing in and (4) your IP address. Additionally, you can provide us with: (1) name and URL of your website; (2) your activity/occupation; (3) country, city, address and ZIP code; (4) name, VAT, telephone and URL of your company, (5) demographic information (such as gender, age, etc) and (6) certain information about your preferences and interests. 

3\. When you download files (images, graphics, vectors) from our site, we collect files downloaded in order to associate those downloads to your account.

4\. All the information collected by our site is provided exclusively by you and might be provided through: (1) Sing Up/Join form; (2) the profile page; (3) our contact form; (4) through other not mandatory forms/surveys across the site or (5) when you make a support query. The only exception to this is your IP address. 

### How we use your Personal Information

1\. We use the Personal Information collected from you for the following purposes: (1) To enable you to sign in to the Website and access member-only features; (2) processing orders and invoices; (3) sending updates of terms, products and promotions; (4) for improving the quality of our services and deliver a better customer experience, and (5) to contact you in relation to your use of the Website. 

2\. We don't use the information provided by you to make automated decisions.

### **Why we need your Personal Information**

1\. Some information provided by you is necessary to use our site. To sign up and log in we need your email. if you make purchases and want the invoice issued to certain company or person, information like name/company name, VAT ID, address and location is needed to be filled in your profile page. Additionally, more specific information like your location, interests, activity among others, might be used to customise your experience across the site. 

### Cross Border Data Transfers

1\. We are based in Uruguay, most of the data we process is handled in our country and stored within the European Union, United States & Canada. To provide you with certain services including some third-party services (newsletter, live chat, payments), we may share your information cross borders. In order to fully protect our users, when we transfer data cross-border we take care where possible, to work with service providers who we believe maintain an acceptable standard of data security compliance. Commonly General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) compliance. 

### **Security** & Safety

1\. We process all personal information in the strictest confidentiality and employ proper technical and organisational measures as required by applicable regulations.

2\. We work under industry-standard encryption to protect your data in transit. This is commonly referred to as transport layer security (“TLS”) or secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology.

3\. When making purchases on Vexels (individual licenses or recurring subscriptions), we use trusted secure payment processors to take payment on our behalf. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.   
We use 2 payment processors/gateways which work also under strict confidential reglamentations which are:

  * BlueSnap.com - Its privacy policy can be checked [here](https://home.bluesnap.com/privacy-policy/)
  * PayPal.com - Its privacy policy can be checked [here](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

### **Cookies**

**  
** 1\. By using the Website, you are agreeing that we can place cookies on your device.

2\. Cookies in general are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user's device. 

3\. Cookies perform different functions, such as allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, improving the user experience, and ensuring that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.

4\. We use cookies to help you navigate the Website efficiently and perform certain functions. For example, cookies allow us to remember your login details to save you from having to type your username and password every time they visit us, or move from page to page.

5\. If you do not want cookies, your web browser has settings which allow you to control how you browse websites. These include settings to manage your cookies. Check your browser’s help information.

### **Accessing and correcting your Personal Information**

**  
** 1\. If you would like to access or modify your Personal Information stored on our servers, you can do so in your profile after login in on our site. If you want to permanently delete your account and all your information please contact us at the address mentioned in the contacts section below of these Policies.  

2\. You can request to contact us through email or our site’s contact form, which forms a report with all stored personal information associated to your account, so we know who’s contacting us.   

### **Third-parties we share data with**

1\. Vexels uses third-party services, including live chat (intercom), email newsletter (mailjet) and payment processor gateways (see section 'Security & Safety'). When using our site we may transfer your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide a specific service. Those service providers are carefully selected by Vexels and they operate in compliance with relevant data law.

2\. The present Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control even if you have accessed the services through our website. Our Site may feature services that are not owned or controlled by us. Once you leave our website, we neither control nor have responsibility for third-party sites, their content, or their privacy practices. 

3\. We may need to share your information if it’s required by law such as in event of a court case. We will attempt to notify you about any legal demands when appropriate in our judgment, unless prohibited by law or court order, or when the request is an emergency. 

###   
**Amendment of this Privacy Policy**

**  
** 1\. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version on the Website. The new version will become effective on the date it is posted.

### **Retention Period**

**  
** 1\. We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required by law.

### **Children**

**  
** 1\. We do not use the Website to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at info(at)vexels(dot)com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

### **Your consent**

**  
** 1\. By using the Website, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. The term “Processing” includes, but is not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

### **Contacting Us**

**  
** 1\. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how your personal information is handled you can always contact us to:

  * email: info(at)vexels(dot)com
  * contact form in our site
  * call us: +1 650 4526034 
  * or you can mail us to Almirante Harwood 6169, Montevideo Uruguay postal code 11500 

### **Last amendment**

1\. This Privacy Policy has been last amended on May 2018.
